http://www.philosophicalgourmet.com/index.php/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Wiley-Blackwell takes the privacy of its customers very seriously. Please read the following policy to understand how we will treat your personal information when you use our site. If this policy changes then we will let you know via this page, and will give you the opportunity to opt out of any changes which affect you. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.	Our postal address is:
9600 Garsington Road
Oxford, OX4 2DQ
UK
We can be reached via e-mail at customsiteshelp@wiley.com or you can reach us by telephone at +44 1865 776868 or fax at +44 1865 714591.
What information do we collect?
When you use services on the site, we will require information about you to fulfil your request. This information may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, your address and your credit card details. When you supply us with this information you can choose not to receive additional email, post or telephone contact from us by selecting the appropriate options on the web page.	When you view our site by linking from another web page we may store the name of that web page for purposes of internal administration.
We also collect general data about the movement of visitors through our site, but this does not use any personal identifiable information.	It is used to improve web site structure and content.
What are cookies and how do we use them?
Cookies are small amounts of information that are sent from a web server to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive and contain information as to the internet sites you have visited.
We may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you and to personalise your contact with us.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but you can usually change your browser to prevent this, although you may not be able to access some parts of our site without them.
How do we use your information?
We will use the information you give us within Blackwell Publishing Limited and its associated companies (including Blackwell Publishing Inc):
To notify you occasionally about important changes to our site and new services, and about publications that may be of interest to you.	If you would rather not receive this information, write to us at the above address or email our Data Protection Officer at dpo@oxon.blackwellpublishing.com.
In order to provide some services free of charge we may display advertisements. By knowing our users we are able to deliver specific advertisements and content.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We do not sell, trade or rent the information we get from you on this site to others.
We do share statistical information with other organisations as part of our marketing. These statistics will not include any personal identifying information. We collect this by monitoring traffic on the site and using anonymous data. We can then construct a specific interest group which assists us in improving and marketing our site.
With respect to Ad Servers: we do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.
Where there are links on our site to other sites, the content of those linked sites is not covered by this privacy policy. These other sites will have separate privacy and data collection practices.	We do not have responsibility or liability for these independent policies.
We may disclose information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is: reasonably necessary to comply with the law enforce or apply our terms of business protect our rights and those of our users
What security measures do we use?
All the data we collect from you on our site is protected against unauthorised access. Your personal information is encoded using SSL (secure sockets layer) technology before being sent over the internet. In addition the information you give us is always stored in a database that is not directly connected to the internet.	We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
How can you access or correct your information?
Upon request we will provide you with access to information we maintain about you. You can access this information by writing to us at the above address or emailing our Data Protection Officer at dpo@oxon.blackwellpublishing.com. If you believe we hold incorrect information on you, we will correct this error upon written request.	Please contact our Data Protection Officer for further assistance at:
9600 Garsington Road
Oxford, OX4 2DQ
UK
Residual information will remain in our archive records.
Your consent
By using our website you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide to us.	If we change our privacy policy we will highlight the changes on this page.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may contact us at the above address or phone number.	If you are not satisfied with this response, you may appeal to the Information Commissioner at http://www.dataprotection.gov.uk/.
